<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:fhir="http://hl7.org/fhir/feed" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>IHE FHIR Packages</title>
    <description>New Packages published by IHE, Inc.</description>
    <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/fhir/package-feed.xml</link>
    <generator>IHE, Inc FHIR Publication tooling</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 02:15:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://profiles.ihe.net/fhir/package-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 02:15:43</pubDate>
    <language>en</language>
    <ttl>600</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.iti.mhds#2.2.0</title>
      <description>This Implementation Guide shows how to build a Document Sharing Exchange using IHE-profiled FHIR standard, rather than the legacy IHE profiles that are dominated by XDS and HL7 v2. This Implementation Guide assembles other IHE Implementation guides (Profiles) and defines a Document Registry Actor. (built Mon, Jan 10, 2022 14:10-0600-06:00)</description>
      <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHDS/2.2.0/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHDS/2.2.0/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.iti.mcsd#3.4.0</title>
      <description>The Patient Demographics Query for Mobile (PDQm) Profile defines a lightweight RESTful interface to a patient demographics supplier leveraging technologies readily available to mobile applications and lightweight browser based applications. (built Mon, Jan 10, 2022 13:58-0600-06:00)</description>
      <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/mCSD/3.4.0/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/mCSD/3.4.0/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IHE.ITI.PDQm#2.3.0</title>
      <description>The Patient Demographics Query for Mobile (PDQm) Profile defines a lightweight RESTful interface to a patient demographics supplier leveraging technologies readily available to mobile applications and lightweight browser based applications. (built Mon, Nov 8, 2021 19:29-0600-06:00)</description>
      <link>https://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PDQm/2.3.0/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PDQm/2.3.0/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.mhd.fhir#4.0.2</title>
      <description>ImplementationGuide for IHE IT Infrastructure Technical Framework Supplement Mobile access to Health Documents (MHD) Rev. 4.0.1 normative (built Mon, Nov 8, 2021 19:09-0600-06:00)</description>
      <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHD/4.0.2/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHD/4.0.2/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IHE.ITI.PIXm#3.0.0</title>
      <description>ImplementationGuide for IHE IT Infrastructure Technical Framework Supplement Patient Identifier Cross-referencing for mobile (PIXm) (built Mon, Nov 8, 2021 19:37-0600-06:00)</description>
      <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PIXm/3.0.0/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PIXm/3.0.0/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.pdqm.fhir#2.2.1</title>
      <description>The Patient Demographics Query for Mobile (PDQm) Profile defines a lightweight RESTful interface to a patient demographics supplier leveraging technologies readily available to mobile applications and lightweight browser based applications. (built Thu, Jul 29, 2021 08:29-0500-05:00)</description>
      <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PDQm/2.2.1/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PDQm/2.2.1/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IHE.ITI.PIXm#2.2.0</title>
      <description>ImplementationGuide for IHE IT Infrastructure Technical Framework Supplement Patient Identity Cross-Reference for mobile (PIXm) Rev. 2.2.0 public-comment (built Thu, Jul 29, 2021 08:22-0500-05:00)</description>
      <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PIXm/2.2.0/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/PIXm/2.2.0/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.mhd.fhir#4.0.1</title>
      <description>ImplementationGuide for IHE IT Infrastructure Technical Framework Supplement Mobile access to Health Documents (MHD) Rev. 4.0.1 normative (built Fri, Jun 4, 2021 16:03-0500-05:00)</description>
      <link>http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHD/4.0.1/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHD/4.0.1/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.formatcode.fhir#1.0.0</title>
      <description>This Implementation Guide publishes the IHE vocabulary for FormatCode and the IHE managed ValueSet for FormatCode. Given that the FormatCode is contributed to by many IHE domains, this IG is dedicated to the publication and management of the FormatCode vocabulary.

FormatCode is a metadata element for identifying the technical format that a document follows. This is related to mimeType, but is more specific to the content requirements than the encoding requirement. Therefore a document following a FormatCode may have many mimeType encodings. The FormatCode is also related to the document type (e.g. LOINC document type), but is more specific to the requirements (constraints) of the content.</description>
      <link>https://profiles.ihe.net/fhir/ihe.formatcode.fhir/1.0.0/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://profiles.ihe.net/fhir/ihe.formatcode.fhir/1.0.0/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE, Inc</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 15:03:49 CDT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.mhd.fhir#4.0.0</title>
      <description>The Mobile access to Health Documents (MHD) Profile defines one standardized interface to health document sharing (a.k.a., an Application Programming Interface (API)) for use by mobile devices so that deployment of mobile applications is more consistent and reusable. In this context, mobile devices include tablets, smart-phones, and embedded devices including home-health devices. This profile is also applicable to more capable systems where needs are simple, such as pulling the latest summary for display. The critical aspects of the “mobile device” are that it is resource-constrained, has a simple programming environment (e.g., JSON, JavaScript), simple protocol stack (e.g., HTTP), and simple display functionality (e.g., HTML browser). The goal is, in part, to avoid burdening the client with additional libraries such as those that are necessary to process SOAP, WSSE, MIME-Multipart, MTOM/XOP, ebRIM, and multi-depth XML.

The Mobile access to Health Documents (MHD) Profile defines one pair of actors and a transaction to submit or push new “document entries” from the mobile device to a receiving system. Another set of actors and transactions is used to query a list of “document entries” having specific metadata, and to retrieve a document.

The transactions defined here leverage the document content- and format-agnostic metadata concepts that were initially developed for XDS but simplify them for access in constrained environments including mobile devices. 

The MHD Profile can be used as an API to a Document Sharing exchange using XDS or XCA. The MHD Profile is used by the MHDS Document Sharing solution. The MHD Profile can be used in push solutions alone or as an API to solutions like XDR or XDM. These are further elaborated in Cross Profile Considerations</description>
      <link>https://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHD/4.0.0/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://profiles.ihe.net/ITI/MHD/4.0.0/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE, Inc</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 11:23:29 CDT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ihe.formatcode.fhir#0.2.4</title>
      <description>This Implementation Guide publishes the IHE vocabulary for FormatCode and the IHE managed ValueSet for FormatCode. Given that the FormatCode is contributed to by many IHE domains, this IG is dedicated to the publication and management of the FormatCode vocabulary.

FormatCode is a metadata element for identifying the technical format that a document follows. This is related to mimeType, but is more specific to the content requirements than the encoding requirement. Therefore a document following a FormatCode may have many mimeType encodings. The FormatCode is also related to the document type (e.g. LOINC document type), but is more specific to the requirements (constraints) of the content.</description>
      <link>https://profiles.ihe.net/fhir/ihe.formatcode.fhir/0.2.4/package.tgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://profiles.ihe.net/fhir/ihe.formatcode.fhir/0.2.4/package.tgz</guid>
      <dc:creator>IHE, Inc</dc:creator>
      <fhir:version>4.0.1</fhir:version>
      <fhir:kind>fhir.ig</fhir:kind>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 11:45:49 CDT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
